# **YOJIT SHINDE**

<IT GRADUATE/>

PORTFOLIO | GITHUB | LINKEDIN

As an IT graduate with a strong foundation in technology and a passion for problem-solving, I am equipped with the skills to navigate the ever-evolving digital landscape and drive innovation in the field. With a keen eye for detail and a collaborative mindset, I am ready to contribute my expertise to propel businesses forward.

#### Education

ST. XAVIER'S COLLEGE (AUTONOMOUS), MUMBAI 2020-2023

Bachelor of Science in **Information Technology**.

RAJHANS VIDHALAYA, ANDHERI (CBSE) 2018-2020

**Higher Secondary Education.** 

RYAN INTERNATIONAL SCHOOL, GOREGAON (ICSE) 2008-2018

Primary & Secondary Education.

# **Work Experience**

Mindgate Solutions
Full-Stack Web Developer Intern
(May 2022 - June 2022)

- Worked on the company's recruitment portal, automating the entire candidate onboarding procedure.
- Improved the front-end design.
- Worked with Rest APIs.
- Helped other interns in debugging.

# Volunteering

Caregiver Saathi Student Volunteer (September 2021 - December 2021)

- Undertook Administrative tasks.
- Interviewed a caregiver and wrote an article based on his experience caregiving.

# Skills

Languages
Java | Python | Typescript
Databases
MySQL | PostgreSQL | MariaDb
Frameworks
Spingboot | Django | AngularJS | Bootstrap
Others
Git | GitHub | Postman | Android Studio

### **Projects**

#### **Placeable**

#### **Placement-Cell Web-Application**

A streamlined platform designed to simplify the placement process for students and recruiters while reducing the load on the placement officer.

**Used:** <u>AngularJS, Django, PostgreSQL, Postman, Git,</u> GitHub.

#### **Desklet**

#### **ERM Web-Application**

A Web-Application for Enterprise Resource Management (ERM) activities that manages all the Purchase Orders (PO), Sales Orders (SO) and Materials Received Notes (MRN) of the organization.

**Used:** <u>AngularJS. Springboot. MySQL. Postman. Git.</u> GitHub.